

https://www.mayurdiar.com
maydiar@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mayurdiar in

678.860.0120

ABOUT ME

Forward-thinking UX/UI & Graphic Designer with a certificate in UX/UI from Georgia Institute of Technology, an MBA from Keller Graduate School of Management and a BFA in Graphic Design from The Art Institute of Atlanta, with experience in Adobe CC, Invision, definition & ideation, prototyping and testing, interaction design, branding and HTML/CSS.

EDUCATION

GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

UX/UI Certificate Program Atlanta, GA | 2020

KELLER GRADUATE SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT

Master of Business Administration – Business Administration and Management Atlanta, GA | 2012

THE ART INSTITUTE OF ATLANTA

Bachelor of Fine Arts - Graphic Design Atlanta, GA | 2004

SKILLS + TOOLS

DESIGN SKILLS

User Experience Design
User Interface Design
Product Design
Visual Design
Interaction Design
Graphic Design
Branding + Identity
Typography

PERSONAL SKILLS

Great Communicator
Problem Solver
Critical Thinker
Detail-Oriented
Leadership
Great Time Management
Organized
Collaborative

UX METHODS

Research + Analysis
User Personas
Ideation
Wireframing
Prototyping
Usability Testing
Evaluation + Iteration

TOOLS



WORK EXPERIENCE

EQUIFAX

Lead UX/UI Designer Atlanta, GA | October 2021 - Present

CIOX HEALTH

UX Design Engineer
Alpharetta, GA | March 2021 - October 2021

- Collaborated with team members to analyze and make recommendations to improve current internal and external software and applications and build concepts for future applications.
- Created low-fidelity sketches and wireframes that represent the proposed value for stakeholders, executives, and end-users.
- Built prototypes to streamline the design development process, test the interface elements, and represent the overall vision.
- Conducted user testing to identify potential issues and collect feedback for necessary changes.
- Negotiated engineering changes and roadblocks throughout the construction process and offer solutions to challenges discovered on the way.

COX AUTOMOTIVE

Advertising Operations Lead Digital Media Designer (UX/UI) Atlanta, GA | December 2011 - March 2020

- Created a variety of products, including dataset driven flash ads to complex, user centered UX/UI rich media products for desktop, mobile and tablet.
- Participated in the entire UX process, from concept through completion. Created sketches, wireframes, user flows, low & high-fidelity prototypes and sitemaps.
- Worked with cross-functional groups to maximize new product testing, implementation and troubleshooting.
- Strengthened cross-departmental relationships to identify key growth opportunities within operations.
- Oversaw training and coaching for all new employees that has exceeded new hire performance goals by over 20% since 2015.

COX AUTOMOTIVE

Customer Operations Digital Media Designer Atlanta, GA | May 2007 - December 2011

- Partnered with dealerships in designing online advertising strategies that increased brand power and drove consumer traffic.
- Tested and implemented new digital products to enhance site performance and customer visibility.
- Executed the development of an onboarding system from concept to completion that improved new employee performance over 30%.
- Collaborated with leadership, team members, and various departments to outline departmental needs, and developed a successful strategy to exceed those goals quarterly.